fanjoy.co 2018-12-30

# Privacy - Fanjoy

**FANJOY PRIVACY POLICY**

**_Last Updated_** _: January 26, 2018_

Fanjoy  Co.  (“ **Fanjoy** ,”  “ **we** ,”  “ **us** ,”  or  “ **our** ”)  respects  your  privacy.    This  Privacy  Policy  explains  how Fanjoy collects, uses, discloses, and secures information about you through our website at fanjoy.co (the “ **Site** ”),   and   our   related   web   sites,   networks,   applications,   mobile   applications,   our   electronic communications, including email and text messages, and other services provided by us (together with the Site, the “ **Service** ”).  By using the Service, you consent to the processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, now and as amended by us.

In providing  the  Service,  we  collect  and  obtain  information  about  individual  consumers  (“you”  or  “ **End User** ”) to, among other things, provide you with access to our e-commerce platform that allows fans to purchase merchandise relating to artists and influencers they admire. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the [Fanjoy Terms of Service. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Privacy](https://fanjoy.co/pages/terms) Policy have the meaning given to them in the Fanjoy Terms of Service.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  

Fanjoy collects  information  from  and  about  users of  the  Service  in  a  variety of  ways.  This  information includes:

_Information   You  Provide_.   We  collect  information  you  provide  when  you  use  the  Service  or  otherwise communicate with us. If you register an account with us, we will collect the information you provide, such as your name, email address, and phone number. We will also collect any information you submit through your use of the Service. For example,  if  you are an End User, the information you provide can include your messaging  history and any information included  in your messages via the Service.   We may also collect information through your communications with our customer-support team.

_Device,   Mobile  and  Usage  Information_.  Like  most  online  services,  we  automatically  receive  standard technical, information when you interact with our Service including browser and device information such as  unique  device  identifiers,  mobile  phone  carrier,  internet protocol (IP) addresses (which may identify your  general geographic  location),  browser types,  and the  date and  time of  your  interactions. We also receive information about your interactions with our Service, such as which website pages you visited and how much time was spent on the page.

We may collect this information using cookies or similar technologies. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your device.  Cookies enable us to personalize your experience on the Service, maintain a persistent session, passively collect demographic information, and monitor advertisements and other activities.  Our Service may use different kinds of cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). We may also use software development kits (known as SDKs) or mobile advertising identifiers (for example, an “IDFA” on Apple mobile devices or an “Advertising ID” on Android mobile devices), which function similarly to cookies on mobile devices.  You may reset your IDFA or Advertising ID in the settings on your mobile device.

**Do Not Track.   **Currently, the Service is not designed to respond to “Do Not Track” signals sent from your browser.  For more information more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [www.allaboutdnt.org.](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/)

_Information from Other Sources_. We may obtain information from third parties and sources other than the Service, such as our partners and advertisers.

  **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use information (including your personal information) in a variety of ways to provide our Service and to operate our business, including the following:

_Service Related Usage_. We use the information we collect about and from you for a number of purposes, including:

  * providing and supporting the Service,
  * verifying your identity,
  * analyzing how you use the Service,
  * tailoring features and content to improve your experience with the Service,
  * personalizing your  experience  with  the  Service  through  products,  services,  and  advertising

(including for third party products and services) that are relevant to your interests.

_Communications_.  We  use  your  information  to communicate with  you for  Service-related  purposes.  For example,  we  may send  email to the  email address you  provide  to  us  or  text  messages,  to  verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, responding to questions or requests, system maintenance, and other Service-related purposes.  We may also use your information to send you newsletters and updates.

_Improve our Service_. We use the information that we collect (i) to understand and analyze usage trends and  preferences;  (ii)  to  monitor  and  analyze  the  effectiveness  of  our  Service;  and  (iii)  to  improve  our Service and develop new products, services, features, and functionality.

_Marketing and Advertising_. As permitted by applicable law, we may use information we collect about you for marketing and advertising purposes, such as providing  you with promotional materials (including for third party products and services) that may be useful, relevant,  valuable or otherwise of  interest to you which may be made available to you on or outside of the Service. Where required under applicable law, we’ll obtain your prior consent to send you electronic marketing communications.

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share,  transfer,  or  disclose  your  information,  if  you consent  to  us  doing  so,  as well as  in the following circumstances: 

_Service Providers_. We share information (including your personal information) with our business partners and  service  providers  who  provide  services  to  us  or  to  you  (on  our  behalf),  such  as  web  site management, third party payment processors, information technology, and other similar service providers. We  also  may  share  your  information  (including  your  personal  information)  with  our  parent  company, subsidiaries, joint venturers, affiliates or investors.

_Third Party and Affiliated Marketing Partners_.   We may share, license or sell information (including your personal information) to third parties and affiliated marketing partners for their marketing or advertising purposes, including their online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., direct mail) marketing programs.

Advertising and Analytics Providers.   We also may provide personal information to advertising providers that you already may have relationships with (such as Facebook or Google) so that they can help us tailor our advertisements or reach you when you are on these third-party platforms. These advertising providers as well as our third-party analytics providers may set and access their own cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies  and  they  may  otherwise  collect  or  have  access  to  information  about  you,  including  your Device  and  Usage  Information.  This  Privacy  Policy  does  not  apply  to  the  activities  of  advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies outside of the Service.

_Comply with Legal Requirements_. We may disclose  your information as we believe  to be  necessary or appropriate to: (i) comply with applicable law and legal processes; (ii) respond to requests from public and government  authorities,  including  public  and  government  authorities outside  your  country of  residence; (iii)  enforce our  Terms of  Service; (iv) protect our rights, privacy,  safety, or property, and/or that of  our affiliates, you or others; and (v) allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

_Corporate Transactions_. We reserve the right to transfer your information to service providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a corporate transaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company or we sell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets.

_Aggregate, De-Identified Information_. We may use your data to create aggregate or statistical information that does not directly identify a specific person, and we may share that information. For example, we may share anonymous and aggregated reports and information on user demographics and traffic patterns with third parties.

_Third   Party  Influencers_.  We  may  share  information  collected  from  you  through  the  Service  with  the influencer  whose  merchandise  you  purchased  via  the  Service  for  their  internal  use  in compliance  with applicable  law.  As  permitted  by  applicable  law,  such  influencer  may  also  use  such  information  for marketing  purposes,  such  as  providing  you  with  promotional  materials  that  may  be  useful,  relevant, valuable  or  otherwise  of  interest  to  you.  Where  required  under  applicable  law,  we’ll  obtain  your  prior consent before permitting an influencer to send you electronic marketing communications.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

The Service may contain links to other sites, maintained by third parties. These links are provided only as a convenience to you.  We or our subsidiaries and affiliated companies have no control over, and are not responsible for any content, products or services offered by or found on third party sites, or their privacy policies.  Links to third party sites do not constitute an assumption of liability for or sponsorship, endorsement or approval of these sites or the content contained on these sites.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

We take steps in an effort to treat your information securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the  security  of  any  information  you  provide  to  us.    We  do  not  accept  liability  for  the  unintentional disclosure of your information and you acknowledge and agree that you use the Service and provide us with your information at your own risk.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under 13 years of age, and  no part of  the Service is directed to children under  the age of 13.   If you learn that  your child  has provided us with personal information without your consent, you may alert us at the contact information listed below.   If we learn that we have collected any personal information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.   If you believe we may have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at hello@fanjoy.co.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**  

The Service is intended for users located within the United States. We make no representation that the Service  is  appropriate  or  available  for  use  outside  of  the  United  States.  Access  to  the  Service  from countries or territories or by individuals where such access is illegal is prohibited. If you are visiting our website  from  the  European  Union  or  other  regions  with  laws  governing  data  collection  and  use,  then please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and processing globally.  By  providing  your  information  to  the  website,  you  consent  to  any  transfer  and  processing  in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**YOUR CHOICES**

You  may  always  direct  us  not  to  share  your  personal  information  with  third  parties,  not  to  use  your personal information to provide you with information or offers, or not to send you newsletters, updates, emails or other communications by:

  * sending us an email at hello@fanjoy.co **;** or
  * following the removal or unsubscribe instructions in the communication that you receive.

If  you wish to verify, correct, or  update any of  your personal information collected through the Service, you may contact us at hello@fanjoy.co or the mailing address included in the Contact Us section below. In  accordance  with  our  routine  record  keeping,  we  may  delete  certain  records  that  contain  personal information  that  you  have  submitted  through  the  Service.   We  are  under  no  obligation  to  store  such personal information indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such personal information.   In addition, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove  or  delete  all  of  your  information  from  our  databases  without  some  residual  data  because  of backups or other technology-related reasons.

If you do not want the Service to collect information through the use of cookies, your browser may allow you to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and restrict or disable certain cookies.  Each browser is different, so you should check your browser’s “Help” menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.  Please be aware that if you disable or reject cookies, some features may not work properly.

On your mobile device, you may also have a “Limit Ad Tracking” setting (on iOS devices) or a setting to “Opt out of Interest-Based Ads” (on Android) which allows you to limit the use of information about your use of apps for purposes of serving ads targeted to your interests.   Note that even if  you opt out using these mechanisms, you may still receive advertisements when using the Service.

You can opt-out of receiving further promotional emails from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided  in  the  promotional  email  you  receive  or  by  contacting  us  directly  at  the  email  address  listed below.

You can opt-out of receiving further text messages from us by replying to any message you receive from us, with the text “STOP”.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California  residents are  entitled  once  a  year,  free  of  charge,  to  request  and  obtain certain  information regarding  our  disclosure,  if  any,  of  personally  identifiable  information  to  third  parties  for  their  direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2017 will receive information about 2016 sharing activities). We comply with this law by giving users the ability to tell us not to share personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an email to hello@fanjoy.co. We may need additional information to process your request.

**CONTACT US**

 If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices or if you would like to exercise your rights and choices, please contact us at hello@fanjoy.co or by writing to us at:

12655 W Jefferson Blvd, 4th Floor

Los Angeles, CA 90066

**PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**  

We  may  update this  Privacy Policy  from  time  to  time.  If  we  make  any changes,  we  will  notify  you  by revising the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any revisions that materially change  the  ways  in  which  we  use  or  share  the  information  previously  collected  from  you  through  the Service,  we  will  give  you  the  opportunity  to  consent  to  such  changes  before  applying  them  to  that information.
